Not reject—means to acknowledge.
No rechazar— significa darse cuenta.
[Recalibration | Shastra, Sadhu, Guru, Vaishnav]
[Recalibrar | Shastra, Sadhu, Guru, Vaishnav]
It is just like, if you have a disease, so you are saying, “I should reject this.”
Es justo como, si estas enfermo, y dices, "Debo rechazar esto."
No, we are saying, “First acknowledge that you have this disease.”
No, estamos diciendo, "Primero date cuenta de que tienes esta enfermedad."
Earlier I showed, you know, I have a blood pressure reading instrument.
Antes les mostré, ya saben, tengo un instrumento para medir la presión sanguínea.
It gives your blood pressure and your heart rate.
Te da la presión de la sangre y el ritmo cardíaco.
So, you need to first ... not just reject it,
Entonces, primero necesitas... no simplemente rechazarlo,
but acknowledge it’s giving false readings.
sino darte cuenta de que está dando una lectura equivocada.
That means it needs to be recalibrated.
Eso quiere decir que necesita ser recalibrado.
Doesn't mean you don't need it; it needs to be recalibrated.
No quiere decir que no lo necesitas; necesita ser recalibrado.
So, you need to recalibrate your criteria for selection.
Entonces, necesitas recalibrar tu criterio para seleccionar.
This is what we are talking about in the beginning.
De eso es de lo que hablamos al principio.
What will be the proper calibration?
¿Cuál sería la calibración adecuada?
Sādhu, Śāstra, Guru, Vaiṣṇava— means revealed truth.
Sādhu, Śāstra, Guru, Vaiṣṇava— es decir la verdad revelada.
When you're recalibrated to see things that way, then you can make proper assessments:
Cuando recalibras para ver las cosas de ese modo. entonces puedes hacer una evaluación adecuada;
this is desirable, that is undesirable,
esto es deseable, esto es indeseable,
I should move in this direction and not go that way.
He de moverme en esta dirección y no ir por ese camino.